<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[CUBlockchainUseCases]]></title>
  <link href="http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/"/>
  <updated>2016-06-05T22:20:33-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://www.coderforart.com/">CoderForArt</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google voice search records and keeps conversations people have around their phones – but the files can be deleted]]></title>
    <link href="http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/14651775961070.html"/>
    <updated>2016-06-05T21:46:36-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/14651775961070.html</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
<h2 id="toc_0">Just talking is enough to activate the recordings – but thankfully there&#39;s an easy way of hearing and deleting them</h2>

<p>Link: <a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/google-voice-search-records-and-stores-conversation-people-have-around-their-phones-but-files-can-be-a7059376.html">http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/google-voice-search-records-and-stores-conversation-people-have-around-their-phones-but-files-can-be-a7059376.html</a></p>

<p><img src="media/14651775961070/Screen%20Shot%202016-06-05%20at%2010.18.33%20PM.png" alt="Screen Shot 2016-06-05 at 10.18.33 P"/>     </p>

<p>&quot;Google could have a record of everything you have said around it for years, and you can listen to it yourself.</p>

<p>The company quietly records many of the conversations that people have around its products.</p>

<p><img src="media/14651775961070/Screen%20Shot%202016-06-05%20at%2010.21.02%20PM.png" alt="Screen Shot 2016-06-05 at 10.21.02 P"/></p>

<p>The feature works as a way of letting people search with their voice, and storing those recordings presumably lets Google improve its language recognition tools as well as the results that it gives to people.</p>

<p>But it also comes with an easy way of listening to and deleting all of the information that it collects. That’s done through a special page that brings together the information that Google has on you.</p>

<p>It’s found by heading to Google’s <a href="https://history.google.com/history/audio">history page and looking at the long list of recordings</a>. The company has a specific audio page and another for activity on the web, which will show you everywhere Google has a record of you being on the internet.&quot;</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[StashCrypto]]></title>
    <link href="http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/14651717456309.html"/>
    <updated>2016-06-05T20:09:05-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/14651717456309.html</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Link: <a href="http://stashcrypto.com">http://stashcrypto.com</a>
## Open Transaction standard protocols </li>
</ul>

<h3 id="toc_0">Wallets</h3>

<h2 id="toc_1"><a href="http://stashcrypto.com">http://stashcrypto.com</a></h2>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[[The CU Ledger Summit](http://www.culedger.com/summit)]]></title>
    <link href="http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/14651710225741.html"/>
    <updated>2016-06-05T19:57:02-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://CIVICS.com/CUBlockchainUseCases/14651710225741.html</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>Join us for the CU Ledger Summit</li>
<li>June 29, 2016 - Minneapolis Mn </li>
</ul>

<p> Immediately following the AXFI Conference<br/>
Distributive Ledger Technology is one of the hottest topics in the financial industry, with Banks and Fintech putting millions into research and development. Immediately following the AXFI Conference, BIG, MWCUA and Evernym will hold a special meeting to discuss the latest news in Distributed Ledger Technology and Identity. Identity experts Drummond Reed and Phil Windley will deliver a presentation on Soveriegn Identity and what it means to have your very own Digital Identity . Come find out how the latest technology will solve the age old problem of &quot;too many usernames and passwords&quot; and how the Credit Union Industry will be a leader in this space.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
